{
    "id": "2870743c8e874dbe8cd8a3e0b6e71cc7",
    "title": "Used To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am quite used to ………………….. hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bcc6725b08f14de8a78c4ee1ac6503e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She used to …………………… a lot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "writing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "af73630b7e354349a83ed924bd06a0ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not used to ………………… on the right.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drive",
                "driving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bfa52603d0834126b7cee56d734e1d2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………., but now I have stopped.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was used to smoking",
                "used to smoke",
                "used to smoking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "de8521c1216a4a8fa2e3313f8852d6df"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… western music, but now I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't use to like",
                "didn't use to liking",
                "was not used to liking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c3c6d089b8c4d108a4a4f1d0181ee2b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I found it difficult to get ………………… in such a cold climate.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used to live",
                "used to living"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "27a737f3f8264e2da28531404fe362c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… very hard last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worked",
                "used to work"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7e20ec3416d47148116c2c858f55ae5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. be afraid of spiders.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "was used to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e6d3efc9b35462498a30ef929780ea0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… .. a big car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wasn't used to driving",
                "wasn't used to drive"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "91d6c429310f4b928657526eb833eb16"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................................. hard when I was at university.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "used to work",
                "used to working"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1cfff90b41394a81bc85073717ff5ecb"
        }
    ]
}